constructiondir.com 2014-06-20

# Construction Directory - Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

The given policy covers privacy practices of constructiondir.com Please read the information below to find out how we treat personally and non-personally identifiable information about our visitors.

**Information collection and its usage**  
Here is what we collect: 

  * Non-personally identifiable information

This refers to information that does not identify a specific individual. This information may include the Web site's Uniform Resource Locator ("URL") that you just came from, which URL you next go to, what browser you are using, and/or your Internet Protocol ("IP") address. We may also collect the information about finding and accessing our site. E.g. search engine and search keyword use, a browser with the help of which our site was accessed, operating system and its version, screen resolution, etc. This data is extremely helpful to provide our visitors with the efficient service, to help people find our site quickly, to be able to arrange site elements according to the modern trends in PC usage and customer requirements. 

  * Personally identifiable information

Please note that we do not collect personally identifiable information about our visitors without their consent. Any private information such as names, telephone and fax numbers, e-mail or postal addresses is submitted voluntarily. This information becomes available to us via ï¿½Submit companiesï¿½ online form. According to privacy practice at constructiondir.com we do not disclose any personally identifiable information to third parties. This information is neither sold, nor is it shared or bartered. All the submitted private information is kept secure and protected by means of the modern data protection technologies.

Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such an action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or a legal process.

**Cookies**  
As part of offering and providing customizable and personalized services we use cookies to store and track the information about you. A cookie is a small data text file, which a website stores on your computer's hard drive (if your Web browser permits) that can later be retrieved to identify you to us. Cookies provide us with the non-personally identifiable information.

An outside ad serving company on our site may also store cookies on your computer to track down the information such as your IP address, browser type, the server your computer is logged onto and whether you responded to a particular ad. Depending on the advertiser, cookies will expire (i.e. be automatically deleted) after different lengths of time. Google Adsense service is also used to publish ads on our site. This service places DART cookies to show the ads relevant to the content of the website or page they are on. Googleï¿½s use of DART cookies enables it to serve ads to the users based on their visit to the current site and to other sites on the Internet. A user may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

**Links to Other Websites**  
This document only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. Other sites accessible through our site have their own privacy policies and data collection, use, and disclosure practices. Please consult each site's privacy policy. We are not responsible for the policies or practices of third parties.

**Contact us**  
If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us.
